labarchives.com 2013-04-21

# None

LabArchives, LLC knows that you care how information about you is used and shared and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.

The following details apply to any personal information provided or gathered by LabArchives, LLC.

Your use of this Web Site indicates to us that you have read and accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Statement. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please [contact the webmaster](mailto:support@labarchives.com).

**WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU DO WE COLLECT?**

When you visit our Web Site, you may provide us with two types of information: (1) personally identifiable information that you knowingly choose to disclose, which is collected on an individual basis, and (2) general user information that does not contain personally identifiable information, which is collected on an aggregate basis as you browse the Web Site. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with requested information, you may not be able to access all of our Web Site's content or services.

In addition to providing us with information through the Web site you may also provide us with personally identifiable information that you knowing choose to disclose when registering interest in LabArchives products and/or services.

**Personally Identifiable Information You Choose to Provide.**

We may ask for certain personal information from you for the purpose of providing to you content and/or services that you request. For example, if you indicate an interest in one of our newsletters or Blogs, you are asked to submit your name and e-mail address, which we retain on file, so that we may send you the information that you requested. We may retain a record of users who have contacted us in order to respond properly to questions or concerns and for purposes of future communications and marketing programs.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information We Collect.**

Cookies/ Web server logs: Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web Site utilizes standard technology called "cookies" and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web Site is used. Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web Site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web Site.

You can, of course, disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, LabArchives will not allow you to log in if you disable cookies. You should consult with your browser's provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies.

**HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?**

We use your personally identifiable information to provide you with the information or content that you have requested, and, in some cases, to contact you about our programs, products, features or services. If you no longer wish to receive such information from us, please [contact the webmaster](mailto:support@labarchives.com)[.](mailto:support@labarchives.com)

We use non-identifying information collected on our Web Site in the aggregate to better understand how our users interact with the Web Site and to enhance their enjoyment and experience. For example, we may use the information to improve the design and content of our Web Site or to analyze the programs and services that we offer.

We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Our employees, agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect the information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement.

We may provide access to your personally identifiable information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web Site, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights, or to protect the rights and safety of visitors to this Web Site or the public. In those instances, the information is provided only for that limited purpose.

We will not share your personally identifiable information in ways unrelated to those described above without providing you with an opportunity to opt out of such use or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

LabArchives will not provide unaffiliated third parties with access to your email address or other contact information. LabArchives or the LabArchives Affiliates may, from time to time, share with you information about other products and services that we think you may find to be of interest. If you wish to change the types of communications you receive from us, you may do so by modifying your profile at [mynotebook.labarchives.com](http://mynotebook.labarchives.com/), by emailing your request to us at [support@LabArchives.com](mailto:support@labarchives.com "customersupport@carbonite.com"), or by clicking on an appropriate link in any LabArchives email communication to you.

LabArchives may disclose your Personal Information to third parties if we believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with a law, regulation, or governmental or judicial warrant, rule, or order; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of LabArchives; (3) enforce the LabArchives Terms and Conditions of Use and/or this Privacy Policy. LabArchives may also provide access to your Backup Data to government authorities if LabArchives suspects or believes that the data contain child pornography or other prohibited data, or that the data or the LabArchives Products or Services are being used for illegal purposes. LabArchives will provide access to your Backup Data to your surviving spouse and/or your executor upon presentation of a death certificate and identification which LabArchives reasonably believes to be valid and sufficient, or in response to a court order, warrant, subpoena or other judicial or administrative legal process.

**DATA SECURITY**

LabArchives has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your Personal Information in our customer database. Personal Information provided to LabArchives is stored in secure facilities with access restricted to authorized personnel only. Although we make good faith efforts to store the Personal Information we collect in a secure operating environment that is not accessible to unauthorized users, we cannot guarantee complete security.

To provide secure credit card processing when ordering from us, orders placed on our Website are processed through a payment gateway which operates under its own privacy policy. If you choose to purchase or license LabArchives Products or Services online using a credit card, the credit card information is sent to LabArchives using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption, an industry-standard method for protecting data as it travels over the Internet, or a similar encryption technology that may become accepted as an industry standard or better encryption method, in the future ("Transmission Encryption"). LabArchives does not store your credit card information.  To learn more about our credit card processing vendors and their respective privacy and other policies (which are incorporated by reference into the LabArchives Privacy Policy and Terms or Use by reference) email us at [support@labarchives.com](mailto:support@labarchives.com "customersupport@carbonite.com").

**LINKS**

This Web Site may contain links to third party sites. Please be aware that LabArchives, LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of any third party sites. Please also be aware that the privacy policies of other sites may differ significantly from the privacy policy of this Web Site. Therefore, we encourage our users to read the privacy statement of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by this Web Site.
